Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences records, 1907-2004 RG0010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Departmental files, 1931-1987; RG0010 Series 5; 12 Linear feet (Box 4, Box 8, Box 7, Box 6, Box 5, Box 3, Box 2, Box 1)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Formation of, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Deans' Council Meetings Minutes, 1967-1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Index
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Faculty Advising Committee on Tenure, 1977-1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Track Positions Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Fields of Research (Years unknown), undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Planning Committee, 1978-1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Spring Commencements, 1978-1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Student Advisory Council, 1970-1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Student Handbooks, 1974-1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Student Newsletters, 1965-1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Tool Requirements, 1976-1983 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Winter Convocation, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Historic Preservation, 1974-1980 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Historic Preservation, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - History Department, 1972-1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - History and Public Policy Program, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Human Ecology Program, 1966-1979 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Individual Programs, 1974-1979 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Individual Programs, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Institute for Educational Leadership, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - International Education, Institute of, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - International Services, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - International Relations: Ph.D. Program, 1965-1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - J.D./MA Program, 1971-1976 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Legislative Affairs, 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Library Research, Proposed Course in, 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Logistics Program, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - M.D./M.S. Program, 1968 -1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - M.D./Ph.D. Program, 1969 -1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Mathematics Department, 1958 -1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Medicine, School of, 1960 -1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Microbiology, Clinical M.S. Program, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Microbiology, Department of, 1981 -1983 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Middle States Association Report, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Middle States Association Accreditation, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Middle States Association's Accreditation of Off-Campus Programs, 1977 -1978 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Middle States Association Task Force Committee on Growing Influence of Government on Affairs of the University, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Middle States Association: Periodic Review Report, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Museum Studies, 1974 -1983 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Music Department, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Mycology Program, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1982 -1986 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - National Research Council, 1981 -1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Naval Academy: GWU Agreement, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - News and Public Affairs Office, Office of, 1982 -1983 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - National Institute for the Conservation of Cultural Property Inc., 1984 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Object Conservation Program Proposal, 1980 -1984 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Off-Campus Programs, 1981 -1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Oral Biology Program, 1979 -1983 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Physics Department, 1964 -1983 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Planning and Budget Office, 1971 -1982 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Patent Policy at GWU, 1979 -1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Pathology, Department of, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Periodic Review Steering Committees, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Pharmacology, Department of, 1981 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Philosophy, Department of, 1982 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Philosophy and Social Policy Program, 1980 -1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Physiology, Department of, 1981 -1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Political Science Department, 1959 -1980 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Political Science Department, 1981 -1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - President's Office, 1965 -1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Privacy Rights, 1970 -1978 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Provost, 1981 -1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Provost, Office of, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Program Evaluations, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Program: Classical Archaeology, Classics and History, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Program: German, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Program: Linguistics, 1979 -1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Program: Philosophy, 1969 -1971 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Program: Physics, 1979 -1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Program: Religion, 1979 -1980 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Program: Russian, 1979 -1980 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Psychology, Department of, 1982 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Psychology/American Psychological Association Accreditation, 1982 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Psychology Department, 1963 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Public Policy Master's Programs, 1980 -1982 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Thematic Programs
  - Public Policy Program, 1978 -1981 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Public Policy Program, 1982 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Public Policy (Regulatory Policy), 1980 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Registrar's Office, 1982 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Regulatory Policy Program, 1977 -1982 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Rice, Charles (Chronology), 1976 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Romance Languages and Literature, 1968 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Rowley, David (Chronology), 1972 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Rowley Correspondence File, 1972 -1974 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Samson Hall/Renovations, 1979 -1984 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - School of Government, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Sino-Soviet Studies, 1981 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Slavic Languages and Literature, 1981 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Smithsonian, 1981 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Social and Economic Statistics, 1974 -1978 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Social and Economic Statistics, 1981 -1985 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Social Research Group, 1981 -1986 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Socio-Economic Notes, 1985 -1987 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    Arvil Adams
  - Socio-Economics, Proposal, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Sociology, Department of, 1979 -1980 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Sociology, Department of, 1981 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Social and Organizational Behavioral Program, 1976 -1979 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Solomon, Henry: Chronology, 1979 -1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Solomon, Henry: References, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Solomon, Henry: Miscellaneous, 1976 -1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Solomon, Henry: Economics, 1965 -1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Graduade School of Arts and Sciences Faculty
  - Speech Pathology and Audiology, 1973 -1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Speech and Drama, 1973 -1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Special Studies, MA and MS in, 1976 -1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Special Studies: Telecommunications, 1979 -1980 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Special Studies: Urban Learning, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Special Studies: Women's Studies, 1980 -1982 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Sponsored Research, 1979 -1980 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Sponsored Research Awards and Proposals, 1979 -1982 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Statistics, 1967 -1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Southeastern Universities Research Association, 1981 -1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Student Affairs, Office of, 1980 -1983 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Student Rights and Responsibilities, 1982 -1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Telecommunications Policy Program, 1981 -1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Studies, Center for, 1981 -1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Theatre and Dance, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Trustee Update Fall, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Television Station (GW), 1981 -1982 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer's Office, Vice President Office of, 1980 -1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - University Fall Convocation, 1982 -1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - University Committee on Research, 1969 -1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - University Committee on Research, 1979 -1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - University Faculty Assembly, 1976 -1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - University Faculty Senate Committee on, 1975 -1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Fiscal Planning and Budgeting University Faculty Senate, 1977 -1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - University Faculty Senate Meetings, 1981 -1983 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Memorandum and Minutes University Faculty Senate Planning Council, 1971 -1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - University Library, 1980 -1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - University Senate Research Committee, 1964 -1984 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - University Patent Actions, 1979 -1981 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - University Students, Division of, 1979 -1981 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Veteran's Administration, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Women's Studies, 1979 -1984 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Women's Studies Proposal: A Policy Allied With the Women's Studies Program, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Women's Studies Personnel Action Forms and Appointments, 1973 -1980 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Final Dissertation Announcement Booklets for Columbian College students, RG0010 Series 6
  - Art History (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anatomy (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Biochemistry (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Biophysics (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Biological Sciences (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chemistry (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Counciling (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Biostatistics (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Economics (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Economics (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Education (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - English Language and Literature (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Epidemiology (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Genetics (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Geochemistry (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Geobiology (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Geology (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Germanic Languages and Literature (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - History (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Homp (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Human Ecology (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Human Sciences (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Immunology (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - International Relations (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mathematics (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Microbiology (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Molecular Medicine (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Monc (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Neuroscience (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Organizaional Science (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Pathology (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Pharmacology (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Physics (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Physiology (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Political Science (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Psychology (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Psychology (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Psychology (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Public Pollicy (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Radiological Sciences (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Romance Languages and Literature (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Sociology (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Statistics (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Ritual for Oral Exam (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - American Civilization (Box 2, Folder 26)